BURCU SAHIN

COMPUTER ENGINEERING

- Date of birthday: 02/01/2000 Phone number: +90 533 287 0226
- Email adress: mkalantar01@gmail.com
 LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/burcu-k-253219107

Education

- Lokman Hekim High School
- Iskenderun Technical
 University

Computer engineering

2018 - 2024

SKILLS

- Adobe Photoshop
- HTML-CSS
- C# SQL JavaFx
- Labelimg
- Capcut Canva

Languages

- English B1
- German basic continues

Certificate

 YDS ACADEMY ENGLISH COURSE

B1 CERTIFICATE

ROOM OF COMPUTER
 ENGINEERS

IZMIR BMO SUMMER CAMP CERTIFICATE

About me

I graduated from Iskenderun Technical University, Department of Computer Engineering. I have been trying to work on Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator and After Effects for 1-2 years. I have a week's experience as a video editor. My graduation project is about image processing.

WORK EXPERIENCE INTERN

Teknokent - Turkey/Adana - 07.2019-08.2019

 A simple automation program by doing a voluntary internship on C# and Sql I developed.

Intern

Teknokent - Turkey/Adana - 07.2022-08.2022

 I became interested in Adobe After Effect, concentrated on the program, and learned how to prepare short videos, edit, make presentations, and make short promotional films.

Projects

Automation - 2022

For garden irrigation systems, it can irrigate at the time it is set, with a timer and customer admin panel. I made a C# project that pulls simple data.

Automation - 2023

I automated car rental using Eclipse with JavaFx.

Image processing – 2024

I took 10 5-minute videos shot from 100 meters above, divided the videos into photos with a short code in Python, tagged them with LABELIMG, and developed a project that recognizes cars and people.